<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Declan Gray-Mullen</title>
    <link>//graydh.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Declan Gray-Mullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 12:00:00 -0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//graydh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 22:42:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: dgraymullen@williston.com
Located: Amherst, MA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutemen Equity Fund Portfolio Visualization</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/projects/mef_visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 12:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/projects/mef_visualization/</guid>
      <description>By: Declan    The Minutemen Equity Fund is an undergraduate Isenberg School of Management student-run organization that manages over $250,000 of the UMass endowment. As a member of the fund, I worked as a Junior and then Senior Analyst covering the technology, financial and basic materials sectors. The analysts in each sector make recommendations regarding the fund’s holdings and produce many deliverables along with three stock pitches a semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GZoltar4Tests - Evaluating Spectrum-Based Fault Localization on Flaky Tests</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/projects/gzoltar4tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 12:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/projects/gzoltar4tests/</guid>
      <description>By: Declan    Working with Professors Marius Minea and Yuriy Brun for my undergraduate honors thesis, I modified an existing spectrum-based fault localization (SBFL) tool GZoltar to collect coverage on on test code across many re-execution in isolation. Our goal was to evaluate the effectivness on localizing the fault in the test code. By comparing the coverage between failing and passing test case executions, our tool attempts to locate the source of non-determinism in the test code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring History Through Visualizations</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/projects/data_visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 12:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/projects/data_visualization/</guid>
      <description>By: Declan    In the spring of 2020, I completed a course called Data Visualization (590V) at UMass Amherst. Throughout the class in both its physical and online components, (thanks COVID) we explored both the psychology of visualizations and learned how to implement our own within the javascript D3 library. With a couple great students I met in the class, for our main project we created a set of visualizations to explore data from various Super Smash Melee tournaments hosted at UMass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Drew Plays Clue!</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/projects/nancy_drew_plays_clue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 12:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/projects/nancy_drew_plays_clue/</guid>
      <description>By: Milo and Declan    One of the most iconic classes within the Computer Science Major at the University of Massachusetts Amherst is Introduction to Computation (CS250). It is covers a vast quantity of computer science theory all the way from simple logic to Turing machines. I took the class with Professor Marius Minea in the Fall of 2019 and additionally completed a 1 credit honors colloquium extension to the course with Professor Minea in order to complete a computer science honors requirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//graydh.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 22:42:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//graydh.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Declan Gray-Mullen is a Math Tutor at The Williston Northampton School in Easthampton, MA. He graduated in February 2023 with a M.S Computer during which he conducted research in the LASER software engineering lab and co-taught courses including Data Structures, Data Management and Data Visualization. During undergrad, Declan worked as a Senior Analyst in the Isenberg Minutemen Equity Fund (MEF) and as a firefighter on the Amherst Fire Department Student Force.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
